>> 键盘: 在使用块作用域限定的主题上，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: While we're on the topic
of using block scoping, and
我们讨论的话题是考虑是否
while we're on the topic
of considering whether or
不允许在顶级功能中使用。
not lets at the top level of
your functions are appropriate.
如果你有这种习惯就像你们很多人一样
If you're of the habit,
as many of you are,
在您的功能的顶级使用，并且您仍然要执行此操作。
of using lets at the top level of your
function, and you still want to do that.
我要提醒你还有很多时候你只会去
I'm going to caution you also that there
are lots of times where you're only going
为几行代码使用变量，并且
to use a variable for
a few lines of code, and
你不应该把它扔进范围的顶层
you should not just throw it
into the top level of the scope.
您应该做的是为其创建作用域。
What you should do is create a scope for
it.
打开卷曲的花括号对，并仅为
Open up a curly brace pair and
create a scope just for
使用前缀和剩余变量的三行代码，以及
those three lines of code to use
the prefixed and the rest variable, and
那就别让他们在功能的其他方面存在了
then don't let them exist for
any other part of the function.
不要只是说说说说和前缀
Don't just say let, and prefix, and
在你的功能之上打开一个大撑
rest at the top of your function,
open up a curly brace there.
事实上，我在任何地方都这么做，即使是在声明中。
As a matter of fact, I do that anywhere,
even inside of an if statement.
如果我有一个只需要存在的变量
If I have a variable that
only needs to exist for
有几条线，要做的就是为它做一个街区。
a couple of lines, the way to do
that is to make a block for it.
顺便说下这不是我的新发明
And that's not a new invention of mine,
by the way.
我们已经这样做了
We've done that for
30 年的所有其他编程语言都有块作用域限定。
30 years in every other programming
language that's ever had block scoping.
我们打开卷曲的支架，把它覆盖在块上。
We open up curly brace pairs and
we scope it to the block.
我要说的是让我们用 JavaScript 来做
All I'm saying is let's do
that in JavaScript because it
用其他语言做的好吗
worked really well in other languages,
yes?
>> 扬声器 2: 您是否将此参数完全用于语义，或者
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Are you making this
argument purely for semantics, or
这样做有什么好处呢 ?
is there a performance benefit
to doing something like that?.
>> 凯尔: 你几乎不可能看到或
&gt;&gt; Kyle: It is extremely unlikely
that you would ever see or
能够观察到任何的性能差异。
be able to observe any
performance difference.
有理论上的性能差异，
There are theoretical
performance differences,
就像理论上的一个越线垃圾回收器
like theoretically an offthread
garbage collector could
理论上垃圾会更早地收集
theoretically garbage
collect it slightly earlier.
或者理论上，它会减少关闭的可用空间。
Or theoretically it would reduce
what was available to a closure.
有理论上的原因但实际上
There are theoretic reasons,
but in practice,
你几乎肯定不会有这样的表现。
you almost certainly would not see
a performance difference this way.
>> 凯尔: 我只是说这一点更加明确。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I'm simply saying that
this communicates more clearly.
顺便说一下我故意让我的
And by the way,
I intentionally did put my lets,
它不仅节省了幻灯片上的空间，而且可以帮助您。
it's not just saving space on the slides,
it helps.
但我故意这样做如果我要打开一个街区
But I intentionally do,
if I'm gonna open up a block, just for
有几个变量的存在
the existence of a couple
of variables like that,
我会把我的声明和开场大撑的那条线放在同一条线上
I'll put my declarations on the very
same line as the opening curly brace.
为了让读者很清楚，嘿，这两个是为这个街区创造的，
To make it super clear to the reader, hey,
these two are created for this block, and
它们只为了这个街区的目的而存在
they exist only for
the purpose of the block.
相对来说你得去找
As opposed to,
you have to go looking for whether or
在此作用域中不存在变量。
not there are variables in this scope.
你得把它弄明白
You have to go figure it out.
我想让它变得非常明显
I want it to be super obvious.
>> 凯尔: 我强烈建议您考虑使用更多这些显式
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I strongly recommend that you
consider using more of these explicit
让我们阻止
let blocks,
将您的变量使用的范围缩小到实际情况。
narrowing the scope where you are using
your variables as much as is practical.